为了验证任何一个应用的可理解性，你
To evaluate how accessible any app is, you
能够逐一进行辅助测试的清单。一些步骤
can step through the Accessibility Testing Checklist. Some of
将包含修改在设置选项中的accessibility设置项。
those steps will involve changing the accessibility settings in
一个用户将能够
the setting's app. A user will be able to
选择选项。我们有talkback,captions,
choose from these options. We have Talkback, Captions,
magnification,increased font size，还有更多。我想在这里
Magnification, increased font size, and more. I want to point
特别提一个选项，也就是talkback服务。盲人和
out one item in particular, Talkback service. Blind and
视力障碍的用户能够启用talkback服务。
low vision users can turn on the Talkback service.
它允许他们通过语音反馈对设备进行导航
It allows them to navigate around the device with spoken feedback
在他们与屏幕上的每个UI元素进行交互时。
as they interact with each UI element on the screen. There
存在一些略微不同的手势，比如，选择或者聚焦
are slightly different gestures, for example, to select or to focus
一个选项。如果这是你第一次打开这个服务，
on an item. If it's the first time you turn it
这里有一个教程帮助你一步一步进行。
on, there will be a tutorial that you can step through.
当用户导向到这些元素，talkback服务将朗读
When the user navigates to these elements, Talkback service will read
提供的内容描述。每个没有任何可见文字的UI组件
aloud the context description provided. Every UI component that doesn't have
都有内容描述。
any visible text has a content
使用在清单中的Talkback或者其他辅助功能
description. Using Talkback or another accessibility
将让Sunshine应用发声。找到并修改至少一个
tool from the checklist will let the sunshine out. Find and fix at least one
在应用中的可理解性问题。然后在课程讨论论坛中分享
accessibility issue in the app. Then please share
你做了什么。
what you did in the class discussion forum.